Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Legal Department microfilmed entertainment contracts, 1924-1957 RL.11870
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Radio Contracts, 1927-1948; undated; 4
  - Elgin National Watch--Thanksgiving and Christmas programs, 1942-1943; 106
    - Don Cossack Chorus (also known as Don Cossack Choir), 1942 Nov. 18 (Film-reel 252)
    - Ed Gardner, 1943 Sept. 30 (Film-reel 252)
    - Edgar Bergen, 1942 Nov. 9; 1943 Oct. 7 (Film-reel 252)
    - Ella Mae Morse, 1942 Nov. 26 (Film-reel 252)
    - Elsie Janis, 1942 Nov. 9; 1943 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 252)
    - Folios, 1942 Nov. 26-1943 Dec. 25 (Film-reel 252)
    - Frances Langford, 1943 Nov. 18 (Film-reel 252)
    - Freddie Slack, 1942 Nov. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Gene Krupa, 1942 Nov. 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - Ginny Simms, 1942 Nov. 9; 1943 Oct. 7; Nov. 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - Golden Gate Quartet, 1942 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 252)
    - Gracie Fields, 1942 Dec. 7 (Film-reel 252)
    - Harriet Hilliard, 1942 Nov. 20 (Film-reel 252)
    - Henry Busse, 1943 Nov. 4 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jack Benny, 1943 Nov. 19 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jack Douglas, 1943 Oct. 7 (Film-reel 252)
    - James E. Jordan, 1943 Dec. 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - James Newell, 1943 Dec. 20 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jose Iturbi, 1942 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jose Iturbi, 1943 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 252)
    - Judy Canova, 1942 Nov. 10; 20 (Film-reel 252)
    - Judy Garland, 1942 Dec. 8; 1943 Nov. 24 (Film-reel 252)
    - Ken Carpenter, 1943 Nov. 4 (Film-reel 252)
    - Kenneth (Buddy) Brown, 1942 Dec. 9; 1943 Dec. 7 (Film-reel 252)
    - Lena Horne, 1943 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 252)
    - Loretta Young, 1942 Nov. 17 (Film-reel 252)
    - Lou Irwin, 1943 Oct. 19 (Film-reel 252)
    - Lum and Abner, 1943 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 252)
      Radio comedy duo of Chester Lauck and Norris Goff, active from 1931 until the 1950s.
    - Marian Jordan, 1943 Dec. 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - McMitchells and M.L. Cook, 1942 Nov. 18 (Film-reel 252)
    - O Star of France--Consent, 1942 Nov. 25 (Film-reel 252)
    - Phil Regan, 1942 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 252)
    - Red Skelton, 1942 Nov. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Robert Mitchell Boys Choir, 1942 Dec. 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - Robert Young, 1943 Sept. 25; Nov. 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - Royal Foster, 1942 Nov. 18 (Film-reel 252)
    - Santa Ana Swing Wing Group (War Dept.), 1943 Oct. 27 (Film-reel 252)
    - Spike Jones, 1942 Nov. 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - Susanna Foster, 1943 Nov. 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - The Charioteers, 1943 Nov. 1 (Film-reel 252)
    - The Four Vagabonds, 1942 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 252)
    - The Joint Is Really Jumpin'--Consent, 1943 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 252)
    - The Pied Pipers, 1943 Oct. 1 (Film-reel 252)
    - The Reviewers, 1943 Oct. 1 (Film-reel 252)
    - The Strange Man--Consent, 1942 Dec. 22 (Film-reel 252)
    - Walter Pidgeon, 1942 Nov. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - William (Butch) Lenhart, 1943 Dec. 7 (Film-reel 252)
  - Elgin National Watch--Thanksgiving Show, 1944; 107
    - Alan Reed, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Allan Jones, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Don Ameche, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Ed Gardner, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Edgar Bergen, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Elsie Janis, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Frances Langford, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Garry Moore, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Jimmy Durante, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Ken Carpenter, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Lina Romay, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Lois Collier, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Maazel and Saundra Berkova, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Robert Casadesus, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Spike Jones, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Susanna Foster, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - The Charioteers, 1944 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 404)
  - Fanny Farmer Candy, 1946; 108
    - Folios, 1946 June 11 (Film-reel 442)
    - Woody Klose--Contract never submitted, 1946 (Film-reel 404)
  - Ford Dealers Advertising Fund, 1946; 109
    - Loren L. Watson Jr., 1946 (Film-reel 405)
  - Ford Motor Company, 1944-1948; 110
    - Abe Burrows, 1946 (Film-reel 404)
    - Alfred Drake, 1944 (Film-reel 405)
    - Angel Reyes, 1945 (Film-reel 405)
    - Bob Crosby, 1946 (Film-reel 404)
    - Bob Crosby Show musicians, 1946 (Film-reel 404)
    - Bob Crosby Show musicians, 1946 (Film-reel 405)
    - Constance Keene, 1945 (Film-reel 405)
    - Dinah Shore, 1946-1947 (Film-reel 405)
    - Earnest Chappell, 1945 (Film-reel 404)
    - Folios, 1947-1948 (Film-reel 442)
    - Frances Blaisdell, 1945 (Film-reel 405)
    - Frances Greer, 1944-1945 (Film-reel 405)
    - Frances Greer--Raymond Page Show folios, 1945 Apr.-June (Film-reel 405)
    - Frank Luther, 1944 (Film-reel 405)
    - George Hope, 1946-1947 (Film-reel 405)
    - Jane Froman, 1945 (Film-reel 405)
    - Jeri Sullivan, 1944-1945 (Film-reel 405)
    - Jo Stafford, 1944-1945 (Film-reel 405)
    - John Lund, 1946 (Film-reel 405)
    - Lawrence Brooks, 1944-1945 (Film-reel 404)
    - Lou Bring, 1946 (Film-reel 405)
    - Memo regarding clearance of songs, 1948 (Film-reel 442)
    - Peter Lind Hayes, 1946-1947 (Film-reel 405)
    - Ray Hayer, 1946-1947 (Film-reel 405)
    - Raymond Paige, 1944-1945 (Film-reel 405)
    - RFD America folios, 1948 (Film-reel 442)
    - Robert Emmett Dolan, 1946-1947 (Film-reel 405)
    - Robert Russell Bennett, 1944-1945 (Film-reel 404)
    - The Ford Show--Dinah Shore, 1947 (Film-reel 442)
    - The Fred Allen Show, 1948 (Film-reel 442)
    - Tom D'Andrea, 1946-1947 (Film-reel 405)
    - Tommy Dorsey, 1944 (Film-reel 405)
    - Town Criers, 1946 (Film-reel 405)
  - Ford Motor Company--Stars of the Future, 1944-1945; 111
    - Alfred Drake, 1945 Mar. 2 (Film-reel 405)
    - Alfred Gallodoro, 1945 Feb. 16 (Film-reel 405)
    - Arthur Whittemore, Jack Love, 1945 Feb. 2 (Film-reel 405)
    - Carroll Glenn, 1945 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 405)
    - David Brooks, 1945 Jan. 19 (Film-reel 405)
    - Del Sharbutt, 1944 Dec. 8-1945 Mar. 30 (Film-reel 405)
    - Donald Dame, 1945 Feb. 23 (Film-reel 405)
    - Dorothy Shawn, 1945 Mar. 30 (Film-reel 405)
    - Earl Wild, 1945 Jan. 19 (Film-reel 405)
    - Edward Kane, 1945 Mar. 30 (Film-reel 405)
    - Eugene List, 1944 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 405)
    - Gloria Story, 1945 Feb. 16 (Film-reel 405)
    - Helena Bliss, 1945 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 405)
    - Isaac Stern, 1945 Mar. 2 (Film-reel 405)
    - Lawrence Brooks, 1944 Dec. 8; 15 (Film-reel 405)
    - Leon Fleischer, 1945 Feb. 23 (Film-reel 405)
    - Leonard Rose, 1945 Jan. 12 (Film-reel 405)
    - Mary Martha Briney, 1945 Mar. 2 (Film-reel 405)
    - Maureen Cannon, 1945 Feb. 2 (Film-reel 405)
    - Ossy Renardy, 1944 Dec. 15 (Film-reel 405)
    - Patricia Travers, 1945 Feb. 9 (Film-reel 405)
    - Richard Dyer-Bennet, 1944 Dec. 22 (Film-reel 405)
    - Robert Stuart, 1945 Mar. 16 (Film-reel 405)
    - Rosalind Nadell, 1945 Mar. 9 (Film-reel 405)
    - Vera Appleton, Michael Field, 1945 Jan. 5 (Film-reel 405)
    - Virginia Oswald, 1945 Mar. 23 (Film-reel 405)
    - Yehudi Menuhin, 1944 Dec. 29 (Film-reel 405)
  - Ford Motor Company--The Ford Show, 1945; 112
    - Connie Boswell, Harry Leedy, 1945 Oct. 30; Nov. 20 (Film-reel 405)
    - Dorothy Kirsten, 1945 Apr. 8; 15 (Film-reel 405)
    - Eileen Farrell, 1945 Nov. 13 (Film-reel 405)
    - Folios, 1945 May 13-Dec. 25 (Film-reel 405)
    - Hugh James, 1945 Sept. 16-30; Nov. 6 (Film-reel 405)
    - Jay Blackton, 1945 May 27-June 24 (Film-reel 405)
    - Jo Stafford, 1945 Apr. 22-May 6 (Film-reel 405)
    - Kay Armen, 1945 Apr. 29 (Film-reel 405)
    - Mary Martin, 1945 Nov. 6 (Film-reel 405)
    - Vaughn Monroe, 1945 Oct. 16 (Film-reel 405)
  - General Cigar, 1940-1945; 113
    - Ann Sheridan, 1945 Jan. 28 (Film-reel 405)
    - Anne Baxter, 1945 June 3 (Film-reel 405)
    - Beatrice Lillie, 1945 Feb. 25 (Film-reel 405)
    - Betty Hutton, 1945 May 20 (Film-reel 405)
    - Bonita Granville, 1945 Apr. 1 (Film-reel 405)
    - Carole Landis, 1945 Apr. 8 (Film-reel 405)
    - Constance Bennett, 1945 May 6-27 (Film-reel 405)
    - Dr. Harry Hagen, 1944 (Film-reel 405)
    - Earl Wilson, 1945 (Film-reel 405)
    - Earl Wilson Show audition folios, 1944 Dec. 12 (Film-reel 405)
    - Eddie Cantor, 1945 June 10 (Film-reel 405)
    - Folios, 1942 Sept. 21-1944 Jan. 20 (Film-reel 252)
    - Folios, 1943 July-1944 (Film-reel 405)
    - Frank Fay, 1945 Apr. 15 (Film-reel 405)
    - Frank Sinatra, 1945 Mar. 18 (Film-reel 405)
    - Fred Allen, 1945 Jan. 14 (Film-reel 405)
    - Gertrude Niesen, 1945 Jan. 21 (Film-reel 405)
    - Gloria Swanson, 1945 Feb. 11 (Film-reel 405)
    - Helen Hayes, 1945 Apr. 29 (Film-reel 405)
    - Henry Gladstone, 1944 (Film-reel 405)
    - Ida Lupino, 1945 June 24 (Film-reel 405)
    - Jane Wyman, 1945 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 405)
    - Joan Bennett, 1945 Mar. 25 (Film-reel 405)
    - John Hodiak, 1945 Junly 1 (Film-reel 405)
    - Joseph Rosenthal, 1945 May 6 (Film-reel 405)
    - June Havoc, 1945 Mar. 11 (Film-reel 405)
    - Mary Boland, 1945 Apr. 22 (Film-reel 405)
    - Memo, 1940 (Film-reel 252)
    - Myrna Loy, 1945 Jan. 28 (Film-reel 405)
    - Paul Douglas, 1945 (Film-reel 405)
    - Paul Sullivan, 1943 (Film-reel 405)
    - Raymond Clapper, 1942-1943 (Film-reel 405)
    - Raymond Gram Swing, 1940 (Film-reel 405)
    - Shirley Booth, 1945 June 17 (Film-reel 405)
    - Shirley Temple, 1945 May 13 (Film-reel 405)
    - Tallulah Bankhead, 1945 Jan. 7 (Film-reel 405)
    - Vera Zorina, 1945 Mar. 4 (Film-reel 405)
    - Wallace Beery, 1945 Feb. 18 (Film-reel 405)
  - Grove Laboratories, 1940-1942; 114
    - Folios, 1940 Dec. 16-1942 Mar. 9 (Film-reel 252)
  - International, 1945; 115
    - Folios, 1945 (Film-reel 407)
  - Irving Trust, 1947; 116
    - Folios, 1947 Mar. 23 (Film-reel 442)
  - J. Walter Thompson, 1944; 117
    - Folios, 1944 Mar.-Dec. (Film-reel 409)
  - J.B. Ward Baking, 1941-1943; 118
    - Folios, 1941 Nov. 5-1943 June 16 (Film-reel 254)
    - Judy and Jane folios, 1943 Jan. 15-July 3 (Film-reel 254)
    - Memo--Transferral of Glenn Riggs from NBC to NCAC, 1942 Feb. 5 (Film-reel 254)
  - J.B. Williams, 1943-1947; 119
    - Quincy Howe, 1945-1946 (Film-reel 410)
    - William L. Shirer, 1943-1947 (Film-reel 410)
    - William Shirer folios, 1943 Dec. (Film-reel 254)
  - Johns-Manville, 1941-1948; 120
    - Bill Henry folios, 1944 Apr. 3-Dec. 28 (Film-reel 406)
    - Bill Henry folios, 1947-1948 (Film-reel 442)
    - Folios, 1941 Oct. 3-1943 Dec. 27 (Film-reel 252)
    - Frazier, 1941 Mar. 11; Sept. 26 (Film-reel 252)
    - Fulton Lewis Jr., 1941 Mar. 11; Sept. 26 (Film-reel 252)
    - Lowell Thomas, 1941 Feb. 19; Apr. 3 (Film-reel 252)
  - Kraft Cheese, 1935-1947; 121
    - Alan Hale, 1943 Feb. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Alan Ladd, 1942 July 2 (Film-reel 252)
    - Alan Reed, 1943 June 24-Sept 8 (Film-reel 252)
    - Alec Templeton, 1941 Apr. 15 (Film-reel 252)
    - Allen Jenkins, 1942 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 252)
    - Andrew Tombes, 1942 Oct. 15; Dec. 17 (Film-reel 252)
    - Andy Devine, 1943 Jan. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Anna Mary Dickey, 1941 Aug. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Beans Reardon, 1942 Mar. 25 (Film-reel 252)
    - Benny Rubin, 1941 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - Bert Lahr, 1941-1943 (Film-reel 252)
    - Betty Hutton, 1942 Sept. 17; Dec. 17 (Film-reel 252)
    - Billy Conn, 1941 July 15 (Film-reel 252)
    - Bing Crosby, 1935-1947 (Film-reel 406)
    - Bob Burns, 1935-1941 (Film-reel 406)
    - Bob Crosby, 1943 Apr. 8-Oct. 22 (for Nov. 25) (Film-reel 252)
    - Bob Crosby, 1943 (Film-reel 253)
    - Bob Crosby and Bobcats, 1942 Feb. 18 (Film-reel 252)
    - Bob Hope, 1941 Apr. 4 (Film-reel 252)
    - Bob Hope, 1943 Oct. 19 (Film-reel 253)
    - Brian Aherne, 1941 Feb. 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - Brian Donlevy, 1941 Oct. 30; 1942 July 16 (Film-reel 252)
    - Broderick Crawford, 1942 Nov. 18 (Film-reel 252)
    - C. Lavere, T. Duncan, 1941 May 1-July 31 (Film-reel 252)
    - Carole Landis, 1941 Nov. 27; 1942 May 20 (Film-reel 252)
    - Cass Daley, 1942 Sept. 8-1943 Oct. 5 (Film-reel 252)
    - Cass Daley, 1943 Dec. 27 (Film-reel 253)
    - Cesar Romero, 1942 Jan. 2 (Film-reel 252)
    - Charles Boyer, 1941 June 19 (Film-reel 252)
    - Charles Coburn, 1942 Feb. 12 (Film-reel 252)
    - Charles Lavere, Nathan Scott, Theodore Duncan, 1941 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 252)
    - Charles Ruggles, 1942 Oct. 8; Dec. 31 (Film-reel 252)
    - Chester Morris, 1941 June 5 (Film-reel 252)
    - Claude Thornhill, 1942 Mar. 27 (Film-reel 252)
    - Cliff Edwards, 1942 Dec. 2 (Film-reel 252)
    - Cliff Nazarro, 1941 Mar. 17; 1943 July 7 (Film-reel 252)
    - Colonel Verne C. Snell, 1942 Jan. 13 (Film-reel 252)
    - Connie Boswell, 1941 (Film-reel 406)
    - Cornelius Warmerdam, 1942 Mar. 4 (Film-reel 252)
    - Dame May Whitty, 1942 Aug. 4 (Film-reel 252)
    - Dave Freeman, 1942 May 21 (Film-reel 252)
    - Desi Arnaz, 1942 Aug. 24; Sept. 30 (Film-reel 252)
    - Dolly Loehr, 1941 May 13 (Film-reel 252)
    - Don Ameche, 1941 (Film-reel 406)
    - Donald Crisp, 1941 Feb. 6-1942 July 6 (Film-reel 252)
    - Dorothy Lamour, 1942 Nov. 11; 1943 June 18 (Film-reel 252)
    - Douglas Fairbanks Jr., 1941 Sept. 25 (Film-reel 252)
    - Duke Ellington, 1941 Jan. 8-Oct. 1 (Film-reel 252)
    - Dusolina Giannini, 1941 Dec. 12 (Film-reel 252)
    - Ed Gardner, 1942 Sept. 8; 1943 July 8 (Film-reel 252)
    - Ed Gardner, 1943 Oct. 21 (Film-reel 253)
    - Ed Herlihy, 1947 (Film-reel 406)
    - Eddie Albert, 1942 Sept. 8 (Film-reel 252)
    - Eddie Bracken, 1941-1943 (Film-reel 252)
    - Eddie Foy Jr., 1946-1947 (Film-reel 406)
    - Eddy Duchin, 1946-1947 (Film-reel 406)
    - Edgar Buchanan, 1942 Nov. 3-1943 Feb. 3 (Film-reel 252)
    - Edward Arnold, 1941 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 252)
    - Edward Brophy, 1942 Nov. 4; 1943 June 22 (Film-reel 252)
    - Edward Everett Horton, 1941 Jan. 15; 1942 July 28 (Film-reel 252)
    - Edward Everett Horton, 1945-1946 (Film-reel 406)
    - Ella Mae Morse, 1942 Nov. 28 (Film-reel 252)
    - Emanuel Manheim, 1942 Nov. 25 (Film-reel 252)
    - Ethel Waters, 1941 May 17 (Film-reel 252)
    - Eugenie Baird, 1944-1945 (Film-reel 406)
    - Eve Arden, 1942 Aug. 24; Oct. 23 (Film-reel 252)
    - Fay Bainter, 1941-1942 (Film-reel 252)
    - Fay McKenzie, 1943 Feb. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Florence George, 1941 July 9; Sept. 24 (Film-reel 252)
    - Folios, 1941 Jan. 2-1943 Dec. 31 (Film-reel 252)
    - Frank McHugh, 1940-1943 (Film-reel 252)
    - Frank Morgan, 1943 Oct. 11 (Film-reel 253)
    - Frank Morgan, 1945-1946 (Film-reel 406)
    - Franklin P. Adams, 1943 June 17 (Film-reel 252)
    - Fred Astaire, 1942 June 16 (Film-reel 252)
    - Freddie Slack, Ella Mae Morse, 1942 Nov. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Gail Patrick, 1941 May 7; Aug. 5 (Film-reel 252)
    - Gene Krupa, 1941 Sept. 15 (Film-reel 252)
    - Gene Tierney, 1942 May 1 (Film-reel 252)
    - George Murphy, 1941-1943 (Film-reel 252)
    - George Raft, 1941 Feb. 14-1942 July 28 (Film-reel 252)
    - George Tobias, 1942 Nov. 18 (Film-reel 252)
    - Ginny Simms, 1942 Nov. 3; 1943 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 252)
    - Gray, Hunt and Sargent, 1941 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 252)
    - Guest spots--Jan Rubini, Bob Burns, Cornelia Otis Skinner, Armand Tokatyan, 1935 Sept. 26 (Film-reel 406)
    - Hail K.M.H.--Consent, 1939 Apr. 13 (Film-reel 252)
    - Hall Johnson, 1941 Nov. 17 (Film-reel 252)
    - Hank Ladd, 1947 (Film-reel 406)
    - Hank Luisetti, 1942 Feb. 25 (Film-reel 252)
    - Harold Peary, 1941 Aug. 7 (Film-reel 252)
    - Harry Fields, Marlene Fingerle, 1941 Mar. 7 (Film-reel 252)
    - Harry James, 1942 June 19 (Film-reel 252)
    - Helen Traubel, 1941 Aug. 27 (Film-reel 252)
    - Herbert Marshall, 1941 Oct. 8; 1942 May 7 (Film-reel 252)
    - Humphrey Bogart, 1941 May 15; Nov. 19 (Film-reel 252)
    - Ida Lupino, 1941 July 11; 1942 July 2 (Film-reel 252)
    - Igor Gorin, 1941 Dec. 2-1942 Sept. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Is There a Santa Claus?--Consent, 1942 Dec. 18; 1943 Jan. 8 (Film-reel 252)
    - Isolelle Randolph, 1943 July 28 (Film-reel 252)
    - J. Carroll Naish, 1941 Mar. 17 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jack Carson, 1942 Dec. 17 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jack Carson, Eddie Marr, 1943 Oct. 17 (Film-reel 253)
    - Jack Douglas, 1943 Oct. 5 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jack Teagarden, 1941 Apr. 8; 1942 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jackie Cooper, 1941 Mar. 6; Sept. 17 (Film-reel 252)
    - James Hilton, 1940 Dec. 26-1941 Sept. 5 (Film-reel 252)
    - James Stephenson, 1941 Jan. 2 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jan Struther, 1941 Feb. 28 (Film-reel 252)
    - Janet Blair, 1942 Nov. 19 (Film-reel 252)
    - Janet Gaynor, 1941 Sept. 3 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jarmilla Novotna, 1941 Aug. 8 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jerry Lester, 1941 Apr. 24-July 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jerry Lester, 1941-1942 (Film-reel 406)
    - Jerry Shelton, 1942 Sept. 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jim Jordan, 1943 Apr. 8-May 14 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jimmy O'Brien, 1941 June 12 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jinx Falkenberg, 1941 Nov. 4-1943 Sept. 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jo Stafford, 1945 (Film-reel 406)
    - Joan Bennett, 1941 Aug. 28; Oct. 16 (Film-reel 252)
    - Joan Blondell, 1941 Aug. 7 (Film-reel 252)
    - Joe DiMaggio, 1941 Nov. 4 (Film-reel 252)
    - John Carradine, 1942 Aug. 28 (Film-reel 252)
    - John Garfield, 1941 July 21-1942 June 1 (Film-reel 252)
    - John O'Hara, 1941 Apr. 2 (Film-reel 252)
    - John Scott Trotter, 1937-1946 (Film-reel 406)
    - Johnny Mercer, 1942 Dec. 16 (Film-reel 252)
    - Jose Iturbi, 1941 Aug. 12; Sept. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Josephine Tuminia, 1941 Apr. 16; June 12 (Film-reel 252)
    - Judy Canova, 1942 Oct. 13 (Film-reel 252)
    - June Havoc, 1942 Apr. 2 (Film-reel 252)
    - Kay Aldridge, 1942 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 252)
    - Kay Kyser, 1941 May 13; 1943 May 6 (Film-reel 252)
    - Ken Carpenter, 1945-1946 (Film-reel 406)
    - King Cole Trio, 1946 (Film-reel 406)
    - Larry Adler, 1942 Apr. 3 (Film-reel 252)
    - Laugh Parade--Consent, 1941 Apr. 2 (Film-reel 252)
    - Lauritz Menchior, 1941 Oct. 16 (Film-reel 252)
    - Legal opinions, 1942 (Film-reel 406)
    - Leo Diamond, 1941 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 252)
    - Leo Sherin, 1943-1944 (Film-reel 406)
    - Les Tremayne, 1945 (Film-reel 406)
    - Lester V. Barrey, 1942 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 252)
    - Letters from Camp--Consent, 1942 Sept. 1 (Film-reel 252)
    - Lew Ayres, 1941 Jan. 29 (Film-reel 252)
    - Linda Darnell, 1942 Apr. 30; June 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Liona Massey, 1942 June 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - Lionel Barrymore, 1941 Feb. 25 (Film-reel 252)
    - Lou Holtz, 1941 July 29 (Film-reel 252)
    - Lou Novikoff, 1941 Mar. 6 (Film-reel 252)
    - Lt. Harold B. Roberts, 1942 Feb. 3 (Film-reel 252)
    - Lucille Ball, 1941 Sept. 4-1943 Sept. 13 (Film-reel 252)
    - Lucille Ball, 1943 Dec. 2 (Film-reel 253)
    - Lum and Abner, 1943 Apr. 29; May 13 (Film-reel 252)
    - Lum and Abner, 1943 Oct. 22 (Film-reel 253)
    - Lynn Overman, 1942 June 16 (Film-reel 252)
    - M.F.K. Fisher, 1942 July 16 (Film-reel 252)
    - Madeleine Carroll, 1942 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 252)
    - Major John S. Winch, 1942 Jan. 5 (Film-reel 252)
    - Major Thomas Power, 1942 Jan. 20 (Film-reel 252)
    - Marcel Grandjany, 1941 June 26 (Film-reel 252)
    - Marcy Maguire, 1942 Nov. 16 (Film-reel 252)
    - Margaret Lenhart, 1942 Dec. 4 (Film-reel 252)
    - Marian Jordan, 1943 Apr. 8-May 14 (Film-reel 252)
    - Martha Scott, 1941 July 29-1942 Apr. 30 (Film-reel 252)
    - Martha Tilton, 1941 Aug. 26 (Film-reel 252)
    - Mary Martin, 1941 July 22 (Film-reel 252)
    - Maureen O'Sullivan, 1941 Aug. 21-1942 Aug. 4 (Film-reel 252)
    - Maxie Rosenbloom, 1942 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 252)
    - Melvyn Douglas, 1941 Sept. 24 (Film-reel 252)
    - Men Never Make Passes at Girls Who Wear Glasses--Consent, 1943 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 252)
    - Mickey Rooney, 1942 Feb. 5; 8 (Film-reel 252)
    - Mike Michaelson, 1941 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 252)
    - Milena Miller, 1946-1947 (Film-reel 406)
    - Milt Herth Trio, 1941 Nov. 6 (Film-reel 252)
    - Milton Berle, 1942 Aug. 17; Sept. 30 (Film-reel 252)
    - Music releases, 1942-1944 (Film-reel 406)
    - Nigel Bruce, 1942 Feb. 26 (Film-reel 252)
    - Ogden Nash, 1941 Jan. 22 (Film-reel 252)
    - Oscar Levant, 1941 Jan. 24; 1943 Aug. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Pat O'Brien, 1941 Apr. 14; 1942 Feb. 26 (Film-reel 252)
    - Paul Robeson, 1941 Feb. 3-1942 Feb. 16 (Film-reel 252)
    - Phil Silvers, 1943 Sept. 3; 18 (Film-reel 252)
    - Phil Silvers, 1943 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 253)
    - Piano in the Band--Consent, 1941 Jan. 14 (Film-reel 252)
    - Priscilla Lane, 1941 May 8 (Film-reel 252)
    - Rags Ragland, 1943 Apr. 1-Aug. 19 (Film-reel 252)
    - Ralph Bellamy, 1941 Sept. 4 (Film-reel 252)
    - Raymond Massey, 1941 June 25; Nov. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Raymond Paige, 1945 (Film-reel 406)
    - Raymond Walburn, 1943 July 8 (Film-reel 252)
    - Richard Haydn, 1942 Sept. 17-1943 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 252)
    - Rise Stevens, 1941 Oct. 14 (Film-reel 252)
    - Rita Hayworth, 1941 July 8 (Film-reel 252)
    - Robert Benchley, 1942 Sept. 10 (Film-reel 252)
    - Robert Burns, 1941 Dec. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Robert Coote, 1941 Oct. 2; Dec. 2 (Film-reel 252)
    - Robert Preston, 1942 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 252)
    - Roland Young, 1941 Jan. 2-1942 Feb. 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - Ronald Reagan, 1942 Apr. 6 (Film-reel 252)
    - Rose Bampton, 1941 Oct. 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - Rosemary Lane, 1941 Apr. 10-1942 July 9 (Film-reel 252)
    - Roy Rogers, 1943 May 25 (Film-reel 252)
    - Rudolph Ganz, 1941 Mar. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Russ Morgan, 1941 Mar. 25 (Film-reel 252)
    - Russell Case, 1946-1947 (Film-reel 406)
    - Ruth Hussey, 1941 Nov. 6; 1942 May 20 (Film-reel 252)
    - S. Freed, T. Duncan, 1941 Mar. 27; June 5 (Film-reel 252)
    - Sabu, 1941 Feb. 6; 1942 Apr. 15 (Film-reel 252)
      Stage name of Indian-born actor Sabu Dastagir (1924-1963)
    - Salvatore Baccaloni, 1941 Oct. 30 (Film-reel 252)
    - Sammy Snead, 1942 Jan. 29 (Film-reel 252)
    - Samuel Freed Jr., 1941 Jan. 9; 30 (Film-reel 252)
    - Shirley Temple, 1942 July 14 (Film-reel 252)
    - Spike Jones, 1942 Apr. 14; June 25 (Film-reel 252)
    - Susan Hayward, 1942 Apr. 28 (Film-reel 252)
    - T. Duncan, A. Secrest, C. Lavere, 1941 May 8 (Film-reel 252)
    - T. Duncan, C. Lavere, 1941 Mar. 20-July 17 (Film-reel 252)
    - T. Duncan, G.P. Gran, 1941 July 10-Aug. 21 (Film-reel 252)
    - T. Duncan, M. Ellington, 1941 May 29 (Film-reel 252)
    - T. Duncan, S. Freed, 1941 Aug. 14 (Film-reel 252)
    - T. Duncan, T. Knudson, A. Goupil, S. Freed, 1941 Mar. 6 (Film-reel 252)
    - T. Knudson, A. Gonzales, J. Heredia, 1941 Mar. 4 (Film-reel 252)
    - The Bobcats, 1942 July 15 (Film-reel 252)
    - The Charioteers, 1942-1946 (Film-reel 406)
    - The Inkspots, 1941 Feb. 10 (Film-reel 252)
    - The King's Men, 1942 Apr. 1 (Film-reel 252)
    - The Merry Macs, 1942 Apr. 28 (Film-reel 252)
    - The Milk Hangs Under the Cow--Consent, 1941 Nov. 18 (Film-reel 252)
    - The Mills Brothers, 1947 (Film-reel 406)
    - The Music Maids, 1939-1942 (Film-reel 406)
    - Theodore R. Duncan, 1941 Jan. 2-July 24 (Film-reel 252)
    - Thomas Mitchell, 1942 June 5 (Film-reel 252)
    - Tom Harmon, 1940 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 252)
    - Trudy Erwin, 1942 Dec. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Tyrone Power, 1942 July 2 (Film-reel 252)
    - Veronica Lake, 1941 Nov. 24 (Film-reel 252)
    - Victor Borge, 1941 Dec. 1; 18; 1943 Jan. 25 (Film-reel 252)
    - Victor Borge, 1941-1942 (Film-reel 406)
    - Victor Mature, 1942 Feb. 8 (Film-reel 252)
    - Vincente Gomez, 1941 Feb. 11 (Film-reel 252)
    - Virginia Bruce, 1941 Jan. 22-Oct. 15 (Film-reel 252)
    - Virginia Weidler, 1942 May 14-Nov. 12 (Film-reel 252)
    - Vronsky and Babin, 1941 July 10 (Film-reel 252)
    - Walt Disney, 1942 June 12 (Film-reel 252)
    - Walter Huston, 1941 Nov. 11; 1942 Mar. 31 (Film-reel 252)
    - Walter Pidgeon, 1941 Jan. 9-1942 Mar. 26 (Film-reel 252)